justrelevant.com 2014-04-28

# Just Relevant - Online Advertising

Privacy Policy

Just Relevant is committed to protecting your online privacy while providing you with the most useful and enjoyable Web experience possible.

How we collect and use personal information

Just Relevant does not automatically collect any personally identifiable information. We do collect personal information when you apply for partnership or otherwise voluntarily provide such information. Our services, such as the Partner Resource Center, may use cookies and/or sessions to enhance your online experience. Just Relevant may automatically record information, including the IP address, browser type, and the date and time of your request when you visit our website or use our services.

How we use "cookies"

As you probably know, "cookies" are small pieces of information that some Web sites store on your computer's hard drive when you visit them. 

Just Relevant does not use cookies at this time.

What we provide to third parties

While Just Relevant does not provide any third-party access to your personal information, we may provide third parties with aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and related site information. This data reflects site usage patterns gathered during millions of customer visits to our Web site each month, but it does not contain behavioral or identifying information about any individual member unless that member has given us permission to share that information.

Obtaining your consent

By using our Web site, you give Just Relevant permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. If you apply for partnership at Just Relevant, you authorize Just Relevant to use information you provide to personalize the information we deliver to you and to use your demographic information when calculating aggregate customer data. As a registered partner, you give Just Relevant and our agents permission to send you e-mails related to the services to which you subscribe.

If you are under the age of 18, you must not provide your name, e-mail address, or any other identifying information without the consent of your parent or guardian, or as otherwise provided for by applicable law.

Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Tell us what you think

Just Relevant welcomes your questions and comments about our privacy policy. Please send an e-mail to [brian@justrelevant.com](mailto:brian@justrelevant.com). 

Copyright � 2006 Just Relevant. All rights reserved.
